what's still a long ways off not if we  take the shortcut through the a blow  past ya pass that suit Territory Jesse  we go up through there we're not gonna  have to help no soldiers we get into  trouble red man ain't got no problem  with the black man huh that's for you  why black yeah that's a whole different  story I mean first you enslave black man  its flight the yellow man and then you  kill off the red man so you can snatch  its land for railroads is such character  witness hey man  well if I may approach the bench your  honor first of all I ain't never  personally enslaved nobody sometime you  can kiss my where it is second of all if  there was a train coming through here on  these tracks right now I'd be on it and  you'd be honest half the only difference  would be I'd be gambling on it and you'd  be fetching my chips like a little  houseboy because you can't even cheat  right now can I get a witness  thank Jessica I feel the cracking huh  why'd you let the Indian get him let's  move out