repeat something to try to turn this  fight around a big rig shut those were  to tremendous right hands in the  nosebleed seats  [Applause]  nobilis is gonna let him go  [Applause]  straining Drago seemingly puss trademark  arrest he was close to finishing the  fight you've got to show me something if  not gonna stop it  Dean fight oh good hello I'm calling  this fight  they don't call this [ __ ] between that  prove [ __ ] to nobody look at you look  like they broke  OTB episode Patamon is Montana's  physical vitamin absorbers  bathroom  please  now as we go to Round three Adonis Creed  has been beaten up and bloodied by an  avalanche of power shots from Ivan Drago  in the first two rounds and we'll see  how much Adonis Creed has left them she  tries to stay alive in the dangerous  Windham chuckles as predestiny tries to  hold  fighting on his last legs  Drago on the attack do  the devastating shot to the ribcage  [Music]